OMRI ANIDGAR

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

Tel: 053-2844980 | Email: omria09@gmail.com

Linkedin: https://www.linkedin.com/in/omri-anidgar | Portfolio: https://omria09.github.io

SUMMARY

Full Stack Developer skilled in **JavaScript**, **React**, **Node.js**, **C++** and more. served as a full-stack developer in the IDF and have a great attention to detail and problem-solving skills. Currently pursuing a B.Sc. in computer science at **The Open University**.

PROJECTS

URL Shortener - https://ktzr.lol/

- Developed a URL Shortener using React, HTML, CSS for the frontend and Node.js & Express for the backend, with mongodb as the database.
- Tracks clicks, incorporating google analytics APIs, shortens URLs, and redirects efficiently.
- Deployed via Netlify (frontend) and Railway (Backend), using Cloudflare Workers for CDN and caching.

VOIP Desktop App

- Created a fully-featured desktop app using Electron with a React frontend and Node.js, Firebase & Firestore for the backend.
- Features include video calls, screen sharing, group creation, and chat functionalities.

EXPERIENCE

Full stack developer, IDF - 2021 - 2023

- Developed and maintained a software solution using **JavaScript**, **jQuery**, **Python** (**Django**), and **SQLite**, supporting over 300 critical users.
- Reduced system downtime by 50% through real-time monitoring and automated issue detection and resolution.
- Handled up to 300 automated issue monitoring daily under high-stress conditions.

C++ Instructor, Magshimim - 2022 - 2023

- Managed and lectured a class of 15+ future programmers, achieving a 95% course completion rate.
- Specialized in C++ debugging, testing, and instruction.
- Led teams on multiple programming projects, enhancing collaboration through effective Git version control.

EDUCATION

B.Sc. Computer Science - 2024-Present

The Open University

National cyber program graduate – Magshimim - 2017-2020

LANGUAGES

Hebrew Native English	Fluent
-----------------------	--------